export const flyFishing = [
  {
    id: 1,
    question: '1. Fly fishing requires the use of special rods and reels.',
    answers: ['True', 'False'],
    correctAnswer: 'True',
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question: '2. Fly fishing is most popular in ocean waters.',
    answers: ['True', 'False'],
    correctAnswer: 'False',
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question: '3. Fly fishing line is often thicker than regular line.',
    answers: ['True', 'False'],
    correctAnswer: 'True',
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question: '4. Fly fishing requires the use of live bait.',
    answers: ['True', 'False'],
    correctAnswer: 'False',
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question: '5. Fly fishing allows for long-distance casting.',
    answers: ['True', 'False'],
    correctAnswer: 'True',
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question: '6. Fly fishing is effective in fast mountain rivers.',
    answers: ['True', 'False'],
    correctAnswer: 'True',
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question: '7. Fly fishing does not require special skills.',
    answers: ['True', 'False'],
    correctAnswer: 'False',
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question: '8. Fly fishing can be used to catch both large and small fish.',
    answers: ['True', 'False'],
    correctAnswer: 'True',
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question: "9. Fly fishing is primarily done on the water's surface.",
    answers: ['True', 'False'],
    correctAnswer: 'True',
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question: '10. Fly fishing is not used for catching predatory fish.',
    answers: ['True', 'False'],
    correctAnswer: 'False',
  },
];
